Lands' End All-American Quilt Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Contest Entries, Every item is accessible by the year of entry, the state, folder number, and personal name. Please consult with the reference staff at the Folklife Reading Room. (Box 7-148)
  - 1996 Entries (Box 109-148)
    - New Hampshire (Box 130, Folder 7914-7930)
    - New Jersey (Box 130, Folder 7931-7961)
    - New Jersey (Box 131, Folder 7962-7985)
    - New Mexico (Box 131, Folder 7986-7999)
    - New York (Box 132, Folder 8000-8047)
    - New York (Box 133, Folder 8048-8104)
    - North Carolina (Box 134, Folder 8105-8159)
    - North Dakota (Box 134, Folder 8160-8166)
    - Ohio (Box 135, Folder 8167-8225)
    - Ohio (Box 136, Folder 8226-8283)
    - Ohio (Box 137, Folder 8284-8312)
    - Oklahoma (Box 137, Folder 8313-8334)
    - Oregon (Box 138, Folder 8335-8364)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 138, Folder 8365-8391)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 139, Folder 8392-8454)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 140, Folder 8455-8466)
    - Rhode Island (Box 140, Folder 8467-8470)
    - South Carolina (Box 140, Folder 8471-8501)
    - South Dakota (Box 140, Folder 8502-8512)
    - Tennessee (Box 141, Folder 8613-8555)
    - Texas (Box 141, Folder 8556-8571)
    - Texas (Box 142, Folder 8572-8624)
    - Texas (Box 143, Folder 8625-8653)
    - Utah (Box 143, Folder 8654-8666)
    - Vermont (Box 143, Folder 8667-8672)
    - Virginia (Box 144, Folder 8673-8716)
    - Washington (Box 144, Folder 8717-8725)
    - Washington (Box 145, Folder 8726-8790)
    - West Virginia (Box 146, Folder 8791-8805)
    - Wisconsin (Box 146, Folder 8806-8846)
    - Wisconsin (Box 147, Folder 8847-8893)
    - Wyoming (Box 147, Folder 8894-8905)
    - Contains all oversized materials belonging to the collection: posters, computer printouts and photographs (Box 148 (Oversized box), Folder 8906-8931)
- Series III: Contest Winners 1992, 1994, 1996, Some "slides" and "negatives" may be "positive transparencies." (Box 149-154)
  - 1992 Winners (Box 149-150)
    - 1992- 1st Place National: Webb, Marianne. Correspondence, photos, slides, entry form, survey (Box 149, Folder 8932)
    - 1992- 2nd Place National: Brooks, Kathleen. Correspondence, photos, slides, publication list, quilt pattern book, articles, survey (Box 149, Folder 8933)
    - 1992- 3rd Place National: Keehr, Brenda. Correspondence, photos, slide, leaflet, brochure, compilation of articles, survey (Box 149, Folder 8934)
    - 1992 Alabama Winner: Gresham, Mabel. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8935)
    - 1992 Alaska Winner: Schell, Ann-Lillian. Entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8936)
    - 1992 Arizona Winner: Evans, Jane. Entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8937)
    - 1992 Arkansas Winner: Hearst, Levena. Entry form, photo negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8938)
    - 1992 California Winner: Potter, Maggie. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8939)
    - 1992 Colorado Winner: Klipfel, Leah. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8940)
    - 1992 Connecticut Winner: Pelletier, Sophie. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8941)
    - 1992 Delaware Winner: Morris, Ruth. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8942)
    - 1992 Washington, D.C. Winner: Splitt, Martha. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8943)
    - 1992 Florida Winner: Haywood, Dixie. Photo, slide, survey (Box 149, Folder 8944A)
    - 1992 Florida Winner: Myers, Dorothy. Entry form, photo, survey (Box 149, Folder 8944B)
    - 1992 Georgia Winner: Lutz, Marcia. Entry form, slides, survey (Box 149, Folder 8945)
    - 1992 Hawaii Winner: Arakaki, Nancy. Entry form, photos, negative (Box 149, Folder 8946)
    - 1992 Idaho Winner: Reisch, Lori. Entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8947)
    - 1992 Illinois Winner: Denaxas, Pat. Entry form, slides, survey (Box 149, Folder 8948)
    - 1992 Indiana Winner: Woodfield, Marlene. Entry form, photo, survey (Box 149, Folder 8949)
    - 1992 Iowa Winner: McCabe, Mary Jo. Entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8950)
    - 1992 Kansas Winner: Seay, J. Alex. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8951)
    - 1992 Kentucky Winner: Ramsey, Kathy. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, cloth samples, survey (Box 149, Folder 8952)
    - 1992 Lousiana Winner: Kruelskie, Patricia. Entry form, slides, survey (Box 149, Folder 8953)
    - 1992 Maine Winner: Rosso, Nancy. Entry form, photo, negative, article (Box 149, Folder 8954)
    - 1992 Maryland Winner: Weber, Julia. Entry form, photo negative (Box 149, Folder 8955)
    - 1992 Massachusetts Winner: Bawn, Rosemary. Entry form, slides, survey (Box 149, Folder 8956)
    - 1992 Michigan Winner: Harbison, Edna. Entry form, photo, slide, survey (Box 149, Folder 8957)
    - 1992 Minnesota Winner: Hedin, Susan. Photo, negative, slide, survey (Box 149, Folder 8958)
    - 1992 Mississippi Winner: Baggett, Gladys. Entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 149, Folder 8959)
    - 1992 Missouri Winner: Finlayson, Constance. Entry form, photos, slide, survey (Box 149, Folder 8960)
    - 1992 Montana Winner: Clarke, Eileen. Entry form, slides, survey (Box 149, Folder 8961)
    - 1992 Nebraska Winner: Landkamer, Ginny. Correspondence, entry form, slides, survey (Box 150, Folder 8962)
    - 1992 Nevada Winner: Bolton, Pat. Correspondence, entry form, slides, survey (Box 150, Folder 8963)
    - 1992 New Hampshire Winner: Calistro, Polly. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8964)
    - 1992 New Jersey Winner: Inverso, Therese. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8965)
    - 1992 New Mexico Winner: Manzanares, Helen. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8966)
    - 1992 New York Winner: Dunn, Frances. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slides (Box 150, Folder 8967)
    - 1992 North Carolina Winner: Hall, Jane. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8968)
    - 1992 North Dakota Winner: Haider, Vicki. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slides, leaflet, survey (Box 150, Folder 8969)
    - 1992 Ohio Winner: Vargo, A.V. Entry form, photo negative (Box 150, Folder 8970)
    - 1992 Oklahoma Winner: Kimball, Charlene. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8971)
    - 1992 Oregon Winner: Sugiyama, Yuki. Entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8972)
    - 1992 Pennsylvania Winner: Cameron, Charlotte. Entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8973)
    - 1992 Rhode Island Winner: Burrill, Jean F. Entry form, photos, slides, survey (Box 150, Folder 8974)
    - 1992 South Carolina Winner: Baugh, Catherine. Entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8975)
    - 1992 South Dakota Winner: Paul, Anna Mae. Correspondence, entry form, photos, slides, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8976)
    - 1992 Tennessee Winner: Shaw, Leslie. Entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8977)
    - 1992 Texas Winner: Newman, Terrie. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8978)
    - 1992 Utah Winner: Dick, Betty. Entry form, slide, negative, returned letter (Box 150, Folder 8979)
    - 1992 Vermont Winner: Greenhoe-Bergh, Eliza. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8980)
    - 1992 Virginia Winner: Fraley, Ted. Correspondence, entry form, photo, returned letter (Box 150, Folder 8981)
    - 1992 Washington State Winner: Simmons, Lorraine. Entry form, slide, negative (Box 150, Folder 8982)
    - 1992 West Virginia Winner: Medovic, Cathy. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8983)
    - 1992 Wisconsin Winner: Kailhofer, Patricia. Entry form, photo, slide, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8984)
    - 1992 Wyoming Winner: Ludwig, Janet. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 150, Folder 8985)
  - 1994 Winners (Box 151-152)
    - 1994 1st Place National Winner: Rouse, Kathryn. Correspondence, entry form, slides, survey (Box 151, Folder 8986)
    - 1994 2nd Place National Winner: Holihan, Jane. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, slide, survey (Box 151, Folder 8987)
    - 1994 3rd Place National Winner: Potter, Maggie. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8988)
    - 1994 Judges' Choice Winner: Reynolds, Ruth. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative (Box 151, Folder 8989)
    - 1994 Judges' Choice Winner: Smith, Karen. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8990)
    - 1994 Judges' Choice Winner: Tummings, La Quita. Correspondence, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8991)
    - 1994 Judges' Choice Winner: Denenberg, Rita. Correspondence, negative, slides, survey (Box 151, Folder 8992)
    - 1994 Judges' Choice Winner: Gant, Alice. Correspondence, photo, negative, flyer, post card, articles (Box 151, Folder 8993)
    - 1994 Alabama Winner: Harshbarger, Linda. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slide negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8994)
    - 1994 Alaska Winner: Dubbs, Kathleen. Correspondence, entry form, slides, survey (Box 151, Folder 8995)
    - 1994 Arizona Winner: Evans, Jane. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8996)
    - 1994 Arkansas Winner: Hattaway, Cesarina. Correspondence, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8997)
    - 1994 California Winner: Olson, Noelle M. Correspondence, entry form, photo (Box 151, Folder 8998)
    - 1994 Colorado Winner: Kimball, Annabelle. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 8999)
    - 1994 Connecticut Winner: Smith, Sandra E. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9000)
    - 1994 Delaware Winner: Ziegler, Madge. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9001)
    - 1994 Washington, D.C. Winner: Beecroft, Anne. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9002)
    - 1994 Florida Winner: Haywood, Dixie. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9003)
    - 1994 Georgia Winner: Butler, Barbara. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9004)
    - 1994 Hawaii Winner: Kapaa, Rita. Correspondence, photos, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9005)
    - 1994 Idaho Winner: Sewell, Sonja. Correspondence Photo, negative (Box 151, Folder 9006)
    - 1994 Illinois Winner: Eddy, Ellen Anne. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9007)
    - 1994 Indiana Winner: Woodfield, Marlene. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9008)
    - 1994 Iowa Winner: McCabe, Mary Jo. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9009)
    - 1994 Kansas Winner: Singer, Vivian. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative survey (Box 151, Folder 9010)
    - 1994 Kentucky Winner: Hughes, Margaret. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9011)
    - 1994 Louisiana Winner: Dison, Deanna D. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9012)
    - 1994 Maine Winner: Hire, Dianne. Correspondence, entry form, negative, slides, survey (Box 151, Folder 9013)
    - 1994 Maryland Winner: Erlenborn, Dorothy C. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9014)
    - 1994 Massachusetts Winner: Miller, Dianne. Entry form, slide, negative, postcards (Box 151, Folder 9015)
    - 1994 Michigan Winner: Ballard, Debra. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 151, Folder 9016)
    - 1994 Minnesota Winner: Sells, Audree. Entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9017)
    - 1994 Mississippi Winner: Schutt, Suzanne. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9018)
    - 1994 Missouri Winner: Bryant, Jill D. Correspondence, photos, survey (Box 152, Folder 9019)
    - 1994 Montana Winner: Goff, Candy. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9020)
    - 1994 Nebraska Winner: Koehler, Fran. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9021)
    - 1994 Nevada Winner: Allison, Mary Ann K. Correspondence, entry form, photos, returned letter (Box 152, Folder 9022)
    - 1994 New Hampshire Winner: Patch, Adele. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9023)
    - 1994 New Jersey Winner: Thompson, Judith. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9024)
    - 1994 New Mexico Winner: Gould, Patricia. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9025)
    - 1994 New York Winner: Strasberg, Lois. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9026)
    - 1994 North Carolina Winner: Wortman, Penelope. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9027)
    - 1994 North Dakota Winner: Zocher, Jodie. Correspondence, entry form, photo negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9028)
    - 1994 Ohio Winner: Null, Nancy. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, newspaper articles, survey (Box 152, Folder 9029)
    - 1994 Oklahoma Winner: Alltizer, Leona. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9030)
    - 1994 Oregon Winner: Hegge, Ken. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, magazine articles, survey (Box 152, Folder 9031)
    - 1994 Pennsylvania Winner: Matthews, Pat. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9032)
    - 1994 Rhode Island Winner: Timby, Deborah. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9033)
    - 1994 South Carolina Winner: Perea, Ilsa. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9034)
    - 1994 South Dakota Winner: Sierra, Lois. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9035)
    - 1994 Tennessee Winner: Clabo, Margo. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, business card, survey (Box 152, Folder 9036)
    - 1994 Texas Winner: Fuquay, Susan. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative (Box 152, Folder 9037)
    - 1994 Utah Winner: Clarine, Barbara. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9038)
    - 1994 Vermont Winner: Fisher, Emma. Correspondence, entry form, negative, returned letter (Box 152, Folder 9039)
    - 1994 Virginia Winner: Clahoun, Frances. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9040)
    - 1994 Washington State Winner: Lee, Kathy. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, slides, survey (Box 152, Folder 9041)
    - 1994 West Virginia Winner: Metz, Pearl. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9042)
    - 1994 Wisconsin Winner: Fahl, Ann. Correspondence, entry form, photos, slide, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9043)
    - 1994 Wyoming Winner: Ludwig, Janet. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 152, Folder 9044)
  - 1996 Winners (Box 153-154)
    - 1996 1st Place National Winner: Goff, Candy. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9045)
    - 1996 2nd Place National Winner: Buckley, Karen, Kay. Photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9046)
    - 1996 3rd Place National Winner: Ott, Carol K. Correspondence, photos, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9047)
    - 1996 Judges' Choice Winner: Averett, Linda. Entry form, photos, slides, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9048)
    - 1996 Judges' Choice Winner: Woodfield, Marlene. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9049)
    - 1996 Judges' Choice Winner: Sewell, Natalie. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9050)
    - 1996 Judges' Choice Winner: McWilliams, Margaret. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9051)
    - 1996 Judges' Choice Winner: McLennand, Sara Ann. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9052)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Lowey-Ball, Herdi B./ Jacksonville Beach Elementary School. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9053)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Noonan, Jo/ Arbor Montessori School. Correspondence, entry form, negative, post card, survey (Box 153, Folder 9054)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Vantlorn, Susannah/ Alpine Elementary. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9055)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Adams, Jo/ Helfrich Park School. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, booklet describing the quilt, survey (Box 153, Folder 9056)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Moss, Durden Pillow. Correspondence, photos, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9057)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Smith, Annette. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9058)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Gorman, Kate/Emerson Magnet School. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9059)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Baer, Cheryl/ The Childrens School. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative (Box 153, Folder 9060)
    - 1996 Kids Quilt: Adler, Debbie/ Walnut Street School. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9061)
    - 1996 Alabama Winner: Wamble, Rhonda Richards (Box 153, Folder 9062)
    - 1996 Alaska Winner: Nancarrow, Ree. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9063)
    - 1996 Arizona Winner: Anderson, Jennifer J. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9064)
    - 1996 Arkansas Winner: Parks, Laura Bailey. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9065)
    - 1996 California Winner: Potter, Maggie. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9066)
    - 1996 Colorado Winner: Berry, Irene. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9067)
    - 1996 Connecticut Winner: McKie, Barbara Barrick. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9068)
    - 1996 Delaware Winner: Schwam, Vicki. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9069)
    - 1996 Washington, D.C. Winner: McCoy, Susanne. Correspondence, photos, negative, slides, survey (Box 153, Folder 9070)
    - 1996 Florida Winner: Styring, Patricia L. Correspondence entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9071)
    - 1996 Georgia Winner: Butler, Barbara. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9072)
    - 1996 Hawaii Winner: Akana, Elizabeth L. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9073)
    - 1996 Idaho Winner: Stewart, Joyce. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9074)
    - 1996 Illinois Winner: Kinnear, Geri. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9075)
    - 1996 Indiana Winner: Hague, Elizabeth A. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9076)
    - 1996 Iowa Winner: Jordan, Ethel Taylor. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9077)
    - 1996 Kansas Winner: Scoggan, Pam. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 153, Folder 9078)
    - 1996 Kentucky Winner: Seigel, Rebekkah. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9079)
    - 1996 Louisiana Winner: Tucker, Daren L. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative (Box 154, Folder 9080)
    - 1996 Maine Winner: Chase, Lori. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, postcard, news clippings, returned letter survey (Box 154, Folder 9081)
    - 1996 Maryland Winner: McWilliams, Margaret. Entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9082)
    - 1996 Massachusetts Winner: Spencer, Jeanette E. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9083)
    - 1996 Michigan Winner: Ingersoll, Patricia. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative (Box 154, Folder 9084)
    - 1996 Minnesota Winner: Haglund, Joan R. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, sketch, survey (Box 154, Folder 9085)
    - 1996 Mississippi Winner: Nicholson, Naomi. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9086)
    - 1996 Missouri Winner: Musik, Ruann. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slides, negative, returned letter (Box 154, Folder 9087)
    - 1996 Montana Winner: Laceky, Carolyn. Correspondence, entry form, photos, slides, negatives, survey (Box 154, Folder 9088)
    - 1996 Nebraska Winner: Burge, Shelly. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9089)
    - 1996 Nevada Winner: Encarnacion, Partricia K. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9090)
    - 1996 New Hampshire Winner: Miller, Janice A. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9091)
    - 1996 New Jersey Winner: Balunis, Evelyn F. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9092)
    - 1996 New Mexico Winner: Gould, Patricia. Correspondence, entry form, negative, slide, survey (Box 154, Folder 9093)
    - 1996 New York Winner: Holihan, Jane. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9094)
    - 1996 North Carolina Winner: Wood, Sherri. Correspondence, entry form, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9095)
    - 1996 North Dakota Winner: Witteman, Lori. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9096)
    - 1996 Ohio Winner: Millward, Hazel I. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9097)
    - 1996 Oklahoma Winner: Prentice, Royce H. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9098)
    - 1996 Oregon Winner: McNutt-Kaestner, Cindy. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slide, negative (Box 154, Folder 9099)
    - 1996 Pennsylvania Winner: Benzo, Terry. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9100)
    - 1996 Rhode Island Winner: Krauss, Joanne L. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9101)
    - 1996 South Carolina Winner: McAllister, Mary Alma. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9102)
    - 1996 South Dakota Winner: Smith, Karen A. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9103)
    - 1996 Tennessee Winner: Aruns, Jane. Correspondence, entry form, slides, negative, returned letter (Box 154, Folder 9104)
    - 1996 Texas Winner: Glaze, Sally. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9105)
    - 1996 Utah Winner: Elmer, Susan. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9106)
    - 1996 Vermont Winner: Fusco, Mary Bartlett. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, returned letter (Box 154, Folder 9107)
    - 1996 Virginia Winner: Elvgren, B.J. Correspondence, entry form, slide, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9108)
    - 1996 Washington State Winner: Gillihan, Anne. Correspondence, entry form, photo, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9109)
    - 1996 West Virginia Winner: White, Norma. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slide, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9110)
    - 1996 Wisconsin Winner: Gaudynski, Diane. Correspondence, entry form, photo, slides, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9111)
    - 1996 Wyoming Winner: Jones, Heather. Correspondence, entry form, photos, negative, survey (Box 154, Folder 9112)
Appendix A: Names of Finalists
1992 FINALISTS
Alabama
None
Alaska
None
Arizona
Leatherberry, Grace
Arkansas
Lake, Edith
California
Copsey, Marjorie
Franz, Betty Jean
Fritz, Laura
Gershon, Janette
Hanley-Rivett, Virginia
Lincoln, Cindy
McCabe, Velma
Swift, Bobbie
Colorado
Jacks, Diana
Jones, Lynne
Pulver, Polly
Trenam, Lois
Connecticut
Cavaiulo, Joanne
Miklave, Sandra
Parisi, Nell
Pessa, Joanna
Delaware
Hoke, Judith